

CONTACTS



House -10, Road -7, Janata Housing, Agargaon, Dhaka -1207.



shithy.mustafa@gmail.com



+8801711395039

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/shithy-

SELF-ASSESSMENT

- Team work.
- Multitasking.
- Good command in Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint and Microsoft Excel.
- Interpersonal and communication skill.

LANGUAGES

- Bengali
- English

TRAINING & SESSIONS

- Participated in Emotional Intelligence and Negotiation Skill training.
- Participated in 3 days PPR (Public Procurement Rules)
 Training, CPTU.
- Participated in Performance Evaluation Session conducted by UNDP.
- Participated in UNDP ToR
 Preparation session.
- Participated in E-nothi
 Management Training.
- Participated in Professional Grooming and Office Etiquette Session.

Shithy Mustafa

HR Professional

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

HR professional with five years of experience focusing on HR and Operational activities. Has expertise on recruitment, individual consultant (IC) procurement, performance evaluation, training and development. Closely worked with UNDP and Government. Has good communication skill in dealing with stakeholders.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HR Assistant

01/03/2021 - Present

Aspire to Innovate (a2i) Programme, ICT Division

- Assisting in HR and procurement activities of the project.
- Processing all the IC UNDP procurement closely with UNDP procurement. (Preparing IC UNDP ToR, preparing technical and financial evaluation documents, processing vendor information etc.)
- Processing IC GoB Recruitment of the project. (Preparing IC GoB ToR, cost estimation sheets, cost approval and other GOB notes, CV screening, preparing technical evaluation documents and interview documents)
- Preparing all types of interview schedule & relevant documents, interview minutes and also assist in conducting interview.
- Assisting in developing IC UNDP procurement plan and TAPP of the Project.
- Raising e-requisitions for IC UNDP procurements on UNDP ATLAS (Assets Management Module)
- Preparing UN payroll action request and a2i payroll sheets.
- Preparing UN email request, ATLAS (UNDP Assets Management Module) access request, UN ID card request.
- Processing performance evaluation of the staffs.
- Regular maintaining and updating a2i website Team and career section, updating and
 posting employee profile, recruitment advertisement etc. Also, assisted in a2i website
 relaunching from HR end.
- Preparing ToR, NoC, results-oriented work plans, appointment letter, experience certificate and circulation about different HR and employee updates and information through email in staff email group.
- Staff database creation and maintenance, updating recruitment tracker.
- Preparing PowerPoint presentation slides and recruitment update reports for different operational and HR meetings.
- Maintaining and updating personnel files & staff leave record.
- Arranging different meetings, trainings, workshops & different knowledge sharing sessions etc.
- Supporting all the project operations activities in full compliance with UNDP rules and regulations.
- Providing overall support and maintaining liaison with the HR and Procurement Cluster of UNDP Country Office and all the staffs and stakeholders of a2i.

Young Professional, HR

Aspire to Innovate (a2i) Programme, ICT Division

- Assisted in HR and procurement activities of the project.
- Processed UNDP and GoB recruitments of the project.
- Prepared interview schedule & relevant documents, interview minutes and also assist in conducting interview.
- Prepared ToR, NoC, appointment letter, experience certificate, payroll management.
- Prepared UN email request, ATLAS (UNDP Assets Management Module) access request, UN ID card request.
- Created and maintained staff database; updated recruitment tracker, a2i website and e-requisition in ATLAS (For UN contracts).
- Prepared PowerPoint presentation slides for Quarterly Preview Meeting (QPR).
- Maintained and updated a2i employee profile on website, posted recruitment advertisement etc.
- Arranged different meetings, trainings, workshops & different knowledge sharing sessions etc.
- Maintained personnel files & staff leave record.
- Supported all the project operations activities in full compliance with UNDP rules and regulations.
- Provided overall support and maintaining liaison with the HR and Procurement Cluster of UNDP Country Office and all the staffs and stakeholders of a2i.

REFERENCE

Md. Mazedul Islam

Project Management Specialist, Aspire to Innovate (a2i) Programme. ICT Division.

Mobile: 01711-236230

Email: mazedul.islam@a2i.gov.bd

Mohammed Naser Miah

Head of Operation, Aspire to Innovate (a2i) Programme. ICT Division.

Mobile: 01712-236211 Email: naser@a2i.gov.bd

Intern

06/06/2017 -06/09/2017

Banglalink Digital Communication Limited Worked at the Device team of Marketing Department Responsibilities:

- Collected quantitative data and creation of database and regular updating the information about competitor's devices of the market.
- Supported the marketing team in daily administrative tasks.

Intern

01/01/2016 -31/03/2016

Social Islami Bank Limited (SIBL)

Worked at the general banking department.

Responsibilities:

- Assisted in general banking services, such as: different types of account opening, helping in money transfer, bill entry, file management etc.
- Dealt with customer service.
- Supported the team in daily administrative tasks.

Education

Course	Major	Institute	Passing	CGPA
			year	
PGDHRM	Human Resource	ABP - Academy of Business	Currently ongoing	
	Management	Professionals		
MBA	Strategic and	University of Dhaka	2016	3.42
	International			
	Management			
BBA	Management	University of Dhaka	2015	3.32